go to the North Pole direct if your
magnetic fields are actually doing a fig
R you're going to be walking you're
going to have to head out
there then follow the magnetic curve you
understand how do they find the North
and South Pole the center they didn't
they never got there as they come up to
it right the F's got this is how your
magnetic fields change and they can walk
through polarities right so the first
guys are in base camp and they're
thinking that the North Pole up there
and out whatever right so they get a
compass and they start walking now
Compass is supposed to go there and
after you turn around this way the comp
is going to turn around still a that one
right yeah yeah so when they started
walking up towards the North Pole like
that this is what
happened and they're still watching this
and they end up back in there that's my
step already I'm make a face cam so they
shook it the damn thing turned around
they walked through it and it didn't
change it never moved it stayed in front
but it walked in a curve now they did it
again so the second time did it you
don't do the first thing again there's
all these alignments of numbering system
that you go through so the second time
they do it this is what
happen cuz went in a different direction
and a different charge and they end up o
we're back at Bas so they shook it the
damn thing turns around and heads back
to there so then they move over you
understand and each different one this
is what they also found as well it's
certain an amount that they never done
by numbers they start walking up and
they
go because the D thing wants to head
down and then they move over about four
want to get
up then want to go want to go that way
and so what happened is around if you're
looking at it around this is a top what
you say there's North Pole what's
happened is they've walked up here and
walked into
there okay they've walked up here and
they've walked into
there okay see the Horseshoes okay and
it's brought them back here and it's
changed they' walked in and out the
fields okay now you talk about in the
Earth the equator line okay so 50
equater line is one side's one way the
other side's the other so like that
shouldn't you be walking up to here and
everything else and your campus does a
flip well
doesn't that's right right and when you
start walking and they did this and
they're following the things this is
what actually happens they end up up at
this end and they never get to it either
and then that comes back down and then
they're doing this got an eight and they
get an eight and they move over and they
get another eight you understand another
eight and then when all those are set
together what you find is that you have
an eight running through this way going
to see it now it doesn't go one way the
fields go both
ways an opposite an reaction this is
where your electricity is all set out
and everything else that your field
effects run two ways at once all
this so it runs two ways at once now it
can't run one way at once for every
action has got to be an opposite and
equal reactions got to be or can't move
can't just make one thing go one way so
Within you made of there did you know
that what you're doing is you're
actually in One Direction you're trying
to throw it that one but at the same
time to make it rotate you're tring to
try that one okay and if you didn't have
the other field on the other side she
just go
bang she wouldn't go over understand
yeah it wouldn't do that so you put
these fields in the Four Points so you
re so you got four points of Cl so you
pong yourong for sure how far can you
bring them in closer and closer and
closer you going to look at the fishing
pipe on there and your girl the coils
are only that far apart massic Co
sideways and there go with the magnets
feels but they're still on off on off
right pull Push Pull push can feel them
that's right you can feel them but it's
a very efficient washing machine very
efficient nor what lets you down is not
the magnets or anything else what let
you down is mechanic or the electrics
Elric up to on this one we're trying to
do is we switch on the electric um
200 Vol y PS
Swit second there was this other one
what we played with and everything else
which is um magnet right on the sides of
a big disc okay and then that went back
to battery 12 Vol batteries okay now it
was on a cam setup to change the pulses
by here so instead of let the magnet
field you coil space do that do a by cam
now what would happen is this this motor
was riing somewhere in about um uh at
first youve taken any revs but we had to
run about a th000 revs now all you do is
take one of those wires and there's two
opposite wires there you got positive
and negative or north and south wire
right take one of those wires go back to
the center rotating shaft not to the
coils just go back to this Center shaft
and touch it one like that in a creat
but did you know jumps a
th000 the thing just jumped up a th000
rep just because of one little touch
from The Wire you do the
other you
know yeah just touch and she flips it
kchen it doesn't build up speed then
slow down it stays it and then you can
do it again and it'll jump again these
things we play with on
but I
don't I can't pay
electricity you might think I'm silly
and everything El all these idiots who
may be looking this he's could be
strange I'm definitely strange but I
wrong with that with that do these for
experimental I don't do these for making
for me or other people I do things no
things and everything else there's
usually not a single
reason does that make sense yeah you
just want
no I don't I find these things and I
don't want to do them and so other
people like to know about them when they
see it and everything else like Peter
wants to shove it up on the net Joe and
Jo the famous Jo I don't go near a
stinking computer hate it I don't read
anybody's stuff I don't check on
anybody's stuff I won't uh look at
anybody else's devices as such or read
up on anybody's technology on you know
anything like Adams generator Motors and
all these other ones are in I don't read
plan and
shellburg I don't read anybody stuff you
know so this T to I'm really interested
in this with the
sale was Farm
a if you can help the F by fixing up the
pl
gooders I'm trying to do a big faor to
them all this you know yeah if you
building a
cell to produce hydrogen to put into a
motor you're going to need something out
the back of your car in yeah but the
semi-trailer lot to make an an amount
enough to keep yourself sustainably
going okay people don't understand it
that you got yourself a um you supposed
to have a vacuum seal
cylinder if that's what you've got there
and that vacuum seal Cinder can't pull
out the amount of stuff that you need in
gas to actually run your vle in volume
so if anybody's out there I don't give
give them this goes out there Joe never
done gas to hook up the motors he never
made harder you oxygen and run them
M this scientist and everybody else just
if anybody puts that out there they're
going to say oh J's full of because
it won't do it you're right that's right
it's not what you're doing you are
changing the frequencies that's right
okay yeah the the cellies for changing a
frequency to change the the way that
your motor runs
without that kind of
fuel so the only thing going into your
engine is air yep the right frequency is
it is it the right frequency that's what
you're really after and is it the air
what the gas is in the air that's
exploding creates not the gases in the
air cuz there are flammable gases in the
air there is and it's the frequency this
if you want did you know that
scientifically all the stuff coming out
of your exhaust B should be exploitable
yeah but it's not because of a catalytic
converter no you you you the ones
without a cal catalytic and everything
else never exploded when it come out the
exhaust either cuz what they don't teach
you is that when you fire these things
in the